<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Comrade Trump</string>


    <!-- Text to display in the list when there are no articles [CHAR LIMIT=NONE] -->
    <string name="no_articles_today">No articles out yet, check back soon!</string>
    <string name="no_articles_week">No articles, must have been a slow week.</string>
    <string name="no_articles_custom">Couldn\'t find any articles. Check your custom dates.</string>

    <!-- Error message when there is no internet connectivity [CHAR LIMIT=NONE] -->
    <string name="no_internet_connection">No internet connection.</string>

    <string name="settings_title">Settings</string>

    <!-- Date Preference strings for settings_main.xml -->
    <string name="start_date_label">Start Date</string>
    <string name="start_date_key" translatable="false">start date</string>
    <string name="start_date_default" translatable="false">2017.01.20</string>
    <string name="end_date_label">End Date</string>
    <string name="end_date_key" translatable="false">end date</string>
    <string name="end_date_default" translatable="false">2017.01.23</string>

    <!-- Article Toolbar -->
    <string name="today_button_string">Today</string>
    <string name="week_button_string">Week</string>
    <string name="custom_button_string">Custom</string>
    <string name="refresh_button_string">Refresh</string>

    <!-- Timeline Items -->
    <string name="timeline_date_4_27_2017">April 27, 2017</string>
    <string name="timeline_event_4_27_2017">The Department of Defense confirms that Michael Flynn is under investigation for failing to disclose payments from a foreign government, despite being previously warned.</string>

    <string name="timeline_date_4_25_2017">April 25, 2017</string>
    <string name="timeline_event_4_25_2017">House Oversight Committee reveals that Michael Flynn may have broken federal law when he applied to renew his security clearance,
        by not disclosing that he received more than $30,000 from a Russian state owned media outlet.</string>

    <string name="timeline_date_4_23_2017">April 23, 2017</string>
    <string name="timeline_event_4_23_2017">Daily beast reports that Senate inquiry is likely understaffed and underqualified.</string>

    <string name="timeline_date_4_21_2017">April 21, 2017</string>
    <string name="timeline_event_4_21_2017">CNN reports that Russian operatives repeatedly made attempts to infiltrate the Trump campaign through Trump advisors.</string>

    <string name="timeline_date_4_19_2017">April 19, 2017</string>
    <string name="timeline_event_4_19_2017">Documents from Russian think tank RISS, show a strategic plan to meddle in US elections including: electing a pro-Russia president,
    damaging Hillary Clinton, and elevating concern about voter fraud.</string>

    <string name="timeline_date_4_13_2017">April 13, 2017</string>
    <string name="timeline_event_4_13_2017">House Democrats call for the FBI to suspend the security clearence of Jared Kushner, due to Kushner failing to
        "disclose key meetings with foreign government officials during his application process."</string>

    <string name="timeline_date_4_12_2017">April 12, 2017</string>
    <string name="timeline_event_4_12_2017">It is confirmed that Paul Manafort\'s investing firm received at least $1.2 million in off the books payments from Pro_Russia
        Ukrainian Group.</string>

    <string name="timeline_date_4_11_2017">April 11, 2017</string>
    <string name="timeline_event_4_11_2017">Report shows that FBI and DOJ obtained warrant to monitor Trump foreign policy advisor Carter Page in summer of 2016.</string>

    <string name="timeline_date_4_06_2017">April 6, 2017</string>
    <string name="timeline_event_4_06_2017">Devin Nunes steps aside as chairman of the House investigation into Trump, as the House ethics committee begins their own investagtion
        into Nunes\' actions.</string>

    <string name="timeline_date_4_03_2017">April 3, 2017</string>
    <string name="timeline_event_4_03_2017">Carter Page met with a Russian intelligence operative in 2013 and provided him documents about the energy industry.</string>

    <string name="timeline_date_3_31_2017">March 31, 2017</string>
    <string name="timeline_event_3_31_2017">The Senate turns down Flynn\'s request for immuniy.</string>

    <string name="timeline_date_3_30_2017">March 30, 2017</string>
    <string name="timeline_event_3_30_2017_1">Michael Flynn offers to testify on Russia-Trump ties in exchange for immunity.</string>
    <string name="timeline_event_3_30_2017_2">Nunes confidential sources are revealed to be two White House officials.</string>

    <string name="timeline_date_3_29_2017">March 29, 2017</string>
    <string name="timeline_event_3_29_2017">Senate Intelligence Committee Chair Sen. Richard Burr (R-NC) announces that 20 witnesses have been asked for interviews as part of
        the Trump-Russia ties investigation.</string>

    <string name="timeline_date_3_27_2017">March 27, 2017</string>
    <string name="timeline_event_3_27_2017">Jared Kushner agrees to testify before the Senate Intelligence Committee.</string>

    <string name="timeline_date_3_24_2017">March 24, 2017</string>
    <string name="timeline_event_3_24_2017">Paul Manafort agrees to testify before the House Intelligence Committee.</string>

    <string name="timeline_date_3_22_2017">March 22, 2017</string>
    <string name="timeline_event_3_22_2017">House Intelligence Committee Chair Devin Nunes, holds a press conference stating that he has evidence that members of the Trump
        team\'s conversations were picked up by intelligence agencies conducting surveillance of foreign targets.</string>

    <string name="timeline_date_3_20_2017">March 20, 2017</string>
    <string name="timeline_event_3_20_2017">The F.B.I. director, James B. Comey, reveals that the FBI is conducting an investigation into the Russian governments efforts to
        interfere in the 2016 election and is looking into any links between the Trump campaign and the Russian government.</string>

    <string name="timeline_date_3_16_2017">March 16, 2017</string>
    <string name="timeline_event_3_16_2017_1">Nazi allied group, Vitézi Rend, claims Trump counter terrorism advisor, Sebastian Gorka is a sworn member.</string>
    <string name="timeline_event_3_16_2017_2">It is revealed that Flynn was paid $33,750 to give a speech on a state-run Russian TV network in December of 2015.</string>

    <string name="timeline_date_3_10_2017">March 10, 2017</string>
    <string name="timeline_event_3_10_2017">The White House acknowledges that they knew that Gen. Flynn\'s consulting firm was under contract with Turkey while he was serving
        as an adviser to Trump.</string>

    <string name="timeline_date_3_02_2017">March 2, 2017</string>
    <string name="timeline_event_3_02_2017">Sessions announces he will recuse himself from any investigations relating to Russia and the Trump campaign.</string>

    <string name="timeline_date_3_01_2017">March 1, 2017</string>
    <string name="timeline_event_3_01_2017">The Washington Post first reports that Sessions, now the attorney general, met twice with Kislyak in 2016.</string>

    <string name="timeline_date_2_27_2017">February 27, 2017</string>
    <string name="timeline_event_2_27_2017">Members of the House Intelligence Committee sign off on a plan to investigate Russia\'s alleged interference in the US elections.</string>

    <string name="timeline_date_2_24_2017">February 24, 2017</string>
    <string name="timeline_event_2_24_2017">FBI refused White House request to knock down recent Trump-Russia stories.</string>

    <string name="timeline_date_2_16_2017">February 16, 2017</string>
    <string name="timeline_event_2_16_2017">FBI officials say that they do not plan to pursue charges against Flynn barring any new information.</string>

    <string name="timeline_date_2_14_2017">February 14, 2017</string>
    <string name="timeline_event_2_14_2017">CNN reports that high-level advisers close to then-nominee Trump were in constant communication during the campaign with Russians
        known to US intelligence.</string>

    <string name="timeline_date_2_13_2017">February 13, 2017</string>
    <string name="timeline_event_2_13_2017">Flynn resigns amid turmoil caused by his lie.</string>

    <string name="timeline_date_2_10_2017">February 10, 2017</string>
    <string name="timeline_event_2_10_2017">Trump states that he is unaware of reports that Flynn spoke about sanctions, a US official later confirms that Flynn and Kislyak
        did speak about sanctions, among other matters.</string>

    <string name="timeline_date_2_09_2017">February 9, 2017</string>
    <string name="timeline_event_2_09_2017">Pence finds out that Flynn lied to him.</string>

    <string name="timeline_date_2_08_2017">February 8, 2017</string>
    <string name="timeline_event_2_08_2017">The Senate confirms Sessions to be the US attorney general.</string>

    <string name="timeline_date_1_26_2017">January 26, 2017</string>
    <string name="timeline_event_1_26_2017">The Justice Department privately warns the Trump administration that Flynn misled administration officials regarding his
        communications with Kislyak and is potentially vulnerable to blackmail by the Russians.</string>

    <string name="timeline_date_1_23_2017">January 23, 2017</string>
    <string name="timeline_event_1_23_2017">Press Scretary Spicer reiterates that Flynn told him sanctions were not discussed in the calls.</string>

    <string name="timeline_date_1_15_2017">January 15, 2017</string>
    <string name="timeline_event_1_15_2017">Vice President Pence tells CBS news that Flynn and Kislyak did not discuss sanctions.</string>

    <string name="timeline_date_1_13_2017">January 13, 2017</string>
    <string name="timeline_event_1_13_2017">Trump spokesman Sean Spicer says Flynn\'s calls to Kislyak focused on the logistics of connecting Trump and Putin.</string>

    <string name="timeline_date_1_12_2017">January 12, 2017</string>
    <string name="timeline_event_1_12_2017">The Washington Post reports that calls between Flynn and Kislyak took place the same day that the sanctions against Russia were announced.</string>

    <string name="timeline_date_1_10_2017">January 10, 2017</string>
    <string name="timeline_event_1_10_2017">At his confirmation hearing, Sessions states that he never was never in contact with the Russians.</string>

    <string name="timeline_date_1_06_2017">January 6, 2017</string>
    <string name="timeline_event_1_06_2017">The top US intelligence agency releases a report concluding that Putin ordered a cyber campaign to help Trump and hurt
        Clinton in the US presidential election.</string>

    <string name="timeline_date_12_29_2016">December 29, 2016</string>
    <string name="timeline_event_12_29_2016_1">Flynn and Kislyak speak regarding the just released sanctions.</string>
    <string name="timeline_event_12_29_2016_2">Obama announces new sanctions against Russia in response to their meddling in the US election.</string>

    <string name="timeline_date_12_28_2016">December 28, 2016</string>
    <string name="timeline_event_12_28_2016">Sergey Kislyak text messages Gen. Flynn.</string>

    <string name="timeline_date_12_25_2016">December 25, 2016</string>
    <string name="timeline_event_12_25_2016">Gen. Flynn and Sergey Kislyak text message holiday pleasantries on Christmas.</string>

    <string name="timeline_date_12_19_2016">December 19, 2016</string>
    <string name="timeline_event_12_19_2016">Gen. Flynn speaks with Sergey Kislyak after the shooting of the Russian ambassador to Turkey.</string>

    <string name="timeline_date_12_12_2016">December 12, 2016</string>
    <string name="timeline_event_12_12_2016">CNN reports that Russian groups also hacked the Republican servers, but chose not to release the information.</string>

    <string name="timeline_date_12_01_2016">December 1, 2016</string>
    <string name="timeline_event_12_01_2016">CNN reports the Paul Manafort has rejoined the Trump team and is helping to shape the new administration.</string>

    <string name="timeline_date_11_18_2016">November 18, 2016</string>
    <string name="timeline_event_11_18_2016">President-elect Trump appoints Army Lt. Gen. Michael Flynn his national security adviser.</string>

    <string name="timeline_date_10_07_2016">October 7, 2016</string>
    <string name="timeline_event_10_07_2016">WikiLeaks begins releasing hacked emails from Clinton campaign manager John Podesta.  The emails continue to be released
        daily for the rest of the campaign.</string>

    <string name="timeline_date_10_04_2016">October 4, 2016</string>
    <string name="timeline_event_10_04_2016">Roger Stone tweets alluding to the release of more hacked emails.</string>

    <string name="timeline_date_09_08_2016">September 8, 2016</string>
    <string name="timeline_event_09_08_2016">Jeff Sessions meets again with Russian ambassador Sergey Kislyak.</string>

    <string name="timeline_date_08_21_2016">August 21, 2016</string>
    <string name="timeline_event_08_21_2016">Roger Stone tweets, alluding to more upcoming email leaks.</string>

    <string name="timeline_date_08_19_2016">August 19, 2016</string>
    <string name="timeline_event_08_19_2016">Paul Manafort resigns his position on Trump campaign the same day the FBI announces investigations into the pro-Russia
        Ukrainian group Manafort had done work for.</string>

    <string name="timeline_date_08_17_2016">August 17, 2016</string>
    <string name="timeline_event_08_17_2016">Roger Stone exchanges private messages with Guccifer 2.0 on Twitter, then posts screenshots on the conversation.</string>

    <string name="timeline_date_08_14_2016">August 14, 2016</string>
    <string name="timeline_event_08_14_2016">The New York Times reports that a pro-Russian political group in the Ukraine likely paid Paul Manafort $12.7 million in undisclosed cash payments.</string>

    <string name="timeline_date_08_08_2016">August 8, 2016</string>
    <string name="timeline_event_08_08_2016">In a speech, Roger Stone states that he is in communication with WikiLeaks founder Julian Assange and that more emails will be coming soon.</string>

    <string name="timeline_date_08_05_2016">August 5, 2016</string>
    <string name="timeline_event_08_05_2016">Trump adviser Roger Stone writes a column for Breitbart News repeating the claim that Guccifer 2.0 was behind the DNC hacks.</string>

    <string name="timeline_date_07_27_2016">July 27, 2016</string>
    <string name="timeline_event_07_27_2016">Trump calls for Russia to continue hacks on the DNC.</string>

    <string name="timeline_date_07_25_2016">July 25, 2016</string>
    <string name="timeline_event_07_25_2016">The FBI announces that it has begun an investigation into the hacked emails.</string>

    <string name="timeline_date_07_22_2016">July 22, 2016</string>
    <string name="timeline_event_07_22_2016">Days before the Democratic National Convention, WikiLeaks releases nearly 20,000 emails hacked from the DNC server.</string>

    <string name="timeline_date_07_18_2016">July 18, 2016</string>
    <string name="timeline_event_07_18_2016_1">Trump  campaign officials J.D. Gordon and Carter Page also had meeting with the Russian ambassador at the Republican Convention.</string>
    <string name="timeline_event_07_18_2016_2">Jeff Sessions has a meeting with Russian ambassador to the US Sergey Kislyak at the Republican National Convention.</string>

    <string name="timeline_date_07_08_2016">July 8, 2016</string>
    <string name="timeline_event_07_08_2016">Telegraph report finds that Trump foreign policy adviser Carter Page gave a lecture in Moscow in which he was highly
        negative toward the US policy toward Russia.</string>

    <string name="timeline_date_06_20_2016">June 20, 2016</string>
    <string name="timeline_event_06_20_2016">Trump fires campaign manager Corey Lewandowski and Paul Manafort emerages as Trump\'s top campaign official.</string>

    <string name="timeline_date_06_15_2016">June 15, 2016</string>
    <string name="timeline_event_06_15_2016">CrowdStrike, a cybersecurity firm hired by the DNC, releases information detailing an attack on the DNC computer network.
        CrowdStrike believes it to be the work of two Russian backed cyberespionage groups, Cozy Bear and Fancy Bear, however Guccifer 2.0 later claims credit.</string>

    <string name="timeline_date_05_19_2016">May 19, 2016</string>
    <string name="timeline_event_05_19_2016">Paul Manafort is promoted to campaign chairman and chief strategist.</string>

    <string name="timeline_date_03_28_2016">March 28, 2016</string>
    <string name="timeline_event_03_28_2016">Trump hires veteran strategist Paul Manafort to head delegate wrangling for the campaign.</string>

    <string name="timeline_date_03_21_2016">March 21, 2016</string>
    <string name="timeline_event_03_21_2016">Trump brings on Walid Phares and Carter Page as foreign policy advisers.</string>

    <string name="timeline_date_02_29_2016">February 29, 2016</string>
    <string name="timeline_event_02_29_2016">Alabama Sen. Jeff Sessions, a supporter and adviser to Trump, endorses Trump\'s presidential campaign.  He is the First Senator to do so.</string>

</resources>
